■
声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：66 wolfRay 亚历9大 paradise 思思 小帝 螃蟹
校对：许愿 时间轴：YY吕伟 leolou
========== 字幕总监制：何何  ==========
Juliet  她是他们的妇产医生
Juliet--she was their fertility doctor,
专门研究怀孕女性的
Studying pregnant women.
他们想要她孩子的原因是为了研究
The reason the others wanted her baby was for research.
-在这个岛上女人怀孕会怎样?  -她们会死
-What happens to pregnant women on this island? Does the--- -they die.
你想让我帮你和你的孩子
You want me to help you and your baby.
我有你问题的答案了
I have answers to your questions,
-不过你现在得跟我走  -这个孩子不是Jin的
-But you have to come with me right now. -The baby isn't Jin's.
我要去看看你的孩子
I'm gonna look at your baby
然后决定妊娠日期
And determine the date of conception.
如果你是在这里怀孕的...
If you got pregnant here...
我们还是要面对现实  渡过难关
We'll cross that bridge when we come to it.
这个孩子是大概八个星期之前怀上的
The baby was conceived about eight weeks ago.
你是在岛上怀孕的
You got pregnant on the island.
那我还剩多少时间?
So how long do I have?
大多数女性
Most of the women made it
能到五  六个月左右
Into the middle of their second trimester.
没有人超过八个月
Nobody made it to their third.
Pidus!
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
我这就上去
I'll be up.
别迟到  Frank
Don't be late, Frank.
Regina
Regina.
Frank
Frank.
我没注意到你
I didn't hear you.
抱歉  我不是故意吓你的
Sorry. I didn't mean to spook ya.
-船长想让我带点食物给这些人  -好
-Captain wanted me to bring these guys some grub. -okay.
你瞧  你的书拿反了
You know, your book's upside-down.
我只是想帮下忙
Just tryin' to help.
我过来登记一下  拿点食物给你们
I thought I'd check in on you guys, bring you some food.
顺便问问  你们感觉如何?
How you feeling, by the way?
-好多了 谢谢  -我们为什么被关起来?
Yeah, much better, thanks. why are we being held captive?
我们和Minkowski的死一点关系也没有
We had nothing to do with minkowski's death.
这个和Minkowski一点关系也没有
This has nothing to do with minkowski.
船长对你们俩逃出医务室
The captain wasn't very happy that you two decided
进入我们的无线电室感到很不高兴
To bust out of sick bay and into our radio room.
我们没想跑  那个门本来就是开着的
We didn't bust out. The door was left open.
我们觉得是你开的门
We assumed it was you.
我干嘛要那么做?
Why the hell would I do that?
你和我们在海滩上的人还有什么联系吗?
Did you have any contact with our people on the beach?
运气不好  他们的电话肯定出了问题
No luck. Something must've happened to their phone.
利马豆?
Lima beans?
抱歉  我们厨房出了点小问题
Sorry. We had a little problem in the kitchen.
呆在这  明白吗?
Just stay put, all right?
我还是想和船长谈谈
I still want to talk to the captain.
不  不行
No, you don't.
Regina
Regina.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
Sayid和Desmond三天前离开的
Sayid and Desmond left three days ago.
为什么他们还没有回来?
Why haven't they come back?
也许他们正和船一起回来
Perhaps they are returning with the ship.
来吧
Now come on...
我们还有更重要的事情要说
We have more important things to talk about.
比如说?
Like what?
让我们来说说孩子的名字
Let's talk about baby names.
很好  你说得越来越好了
Good. you're getting better.
不过 不  Jin
Hmm. But, no, Jin.
现在讨论孩子的名字会带来厄运
It's bad luck to talk about baby names now.
你还迷信?
Superstitious?
我不想让他倒霉
I don't want to Jinx him.
你是说她吧
You mean her.
会是个女孩  是吗?
Oh, it's going to be a girl, is it?
Ji Yeon
Ji Yeon.
我想叫她Ji Yeon
I want to name her Ji Yeon.
我不想说名字的事
I don't want to talk about names.
你不喜欢Ji Yeon这个名字?
You don't like Ji Yeon?
不  这个名字很好
No, it's beautiful.
我会告诉你的
I'll tell you what.
不过我们得先离开这个岛
Let's get off the island first.
然后我们再挑选个名字
Then we can pick a name.
一言为定
Deal.
紧急通信
Emergency services.
我需要救护车...
I need an ambulance...
大概是什么问题?
What seems to be the problem?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant...
我现在觉得出了点问题
and I think something's wrong.
需要帮忙吗?
Can I help you?
你在找什么吗?
Is there something you're looking for?
恩  一个熊猫
Yes...a panda.
在这边
This way, please.
好的
Good.
给我这个
Give me that one.
你想把礼物包起来吗?
Would you like it gift wrapped?
不用了  我还得去医院
No, I have to get to the hospital.
多少钱?
How much is it?
五万
Fifty thousand won.
要去妇产病房?
Maternity ward?
为什么不早说?
Why didn't you say so?
你应该非常高兴才对
You must be very happy...
男孩还是女孩?
Boy or a girl?
我还不知道呢
I...I don't know yet.
别担心
Don't worry.
所有人都喜欢熊猫的
Everyone loves a panda.
好 好  我在路上了
Yes, yes. I'm on my way...
我在路上了
I'm on my way.
我明白
I understand.
祝你好运
Good luck.
Jin!
Kate和Jack回来了
Kate and Jack are back.
发生什么了?
What happened?
你想说在那个红发女袭击我之前还是之后?
You mean before or after the redhead knock me out?
她打了你?
She hit you?
我从Lock的营地往回跑时碰上了她
When I ran into them on my way back from Locke's camp.
她什么要那样做?
Why would she do that?
我想她不会想去解释
I guess she didn't wannhave to explain
她为什么要去一个毒气工厂
Why she was on her way to a poison gas factory.
Juliet告诉Jack说那是个发电站
Juliet told Jack that it was a power station.
Juliet为什么要说谎?
Why would julietie about that?
习惯使然?
Force of habit?
他们为什么要去那里?
Why were they going there?
关掉它  关闭毒气
To turn it off, to deactivate the gas.
我猜他们是去赚女童子军学分
I guess they wanted to earn some brownie points.
你觉得他们真的会救我们吗?
Do you think they're really going to rescue us?
他们在这里这么久
In all the time they've been here,
说了很多事情
They've talked about a lot of things,
不过没有一件是关于救我们的
And none involved rescuing us.
早安
Good morning.
我希望他们解决了厨房的问题
I hope they resolve their kitchen issues.
Sayid
Sayid.
那是什么?
What's that?
一张便签
It's a note.
三天前
Three days ago,
我在Locke的营地时
When I was in locke's camp,
Ben说他在船上有个间谍
Ben claimed he had a spy on this boat.
别相信船长
Don't trust captain
你好
Hello.
我叫sun
My name is Sun.
你好  Sun  我叫Daniel
Hi, Sun hi. I'm Daniel.
需要帮忙吗?
Something I can help you with?
我怀孕两个月了
I'm two months pregnant.
噢  你...
Oh, you're...
哇  那...
Wow, that's...
恭喜啊
Congratulations.
那你是来救我们的吗?
So are you here to rescue us?
这不难回答
It's a simple question.
到底是  还是不是?
Are you or are you not going to rescue us?
这个...
The thing is, ...
实际上也不是我说了算  sun
It's not really my call, sun.
那谁说了算?
Then whose call is it?
谢谢
Thank you.
嗯  能把燕麦粥递给我吗?
Uh, can you pass, uh, the cereal?
英语讲得不错  Jin
Pretty good english, Jin.
我听得懂  但说不好
.. I understand better than i, uh, speak.
是sun教你的  还是自学的?
Has sun been teaching you, or are you just picking it up?
嗯  Sun教的
Uh, sun teach me.
嗯  还有  Sawyer
Uh, Sawyer, too.
Sun讲的更好
Sun is... better.
我想也是
I bet.
嘿  Sun
Hey, sun
觉得怎么样?
How you feeling?
我很好  谢谢
I'm good. thank you.
晨吐已经停了
The morning sickness has stopped,
挺好的
Which has been nice.
很好
That's good.
那么...
Well...
要是需要帮忙  尽管说  好吗?
If you need anything, just let me know, okay?
要来点早餐吗?
Would you like some breakfast?
Jin
你要按我说的做  什么都别问
You need to do as i say and not ask questions.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
你得找到够我们吃两天食物
You need to find food for two days.
二十分钟后去帐篷找我
Meet me at the tent in twenty minutes.
为什么?
Why?
发生什么事了?
What's happened?
我们要到Locke的营地去
We're going to Locke's camp.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
我想再要一瓶那些你给的维他命片
I needed another bottle of those vitamins you gave me,
产前用的
The--the prenatals.
你怎么不早说
You could've just asked.
是啊  我本该早点向你要
You're right. I should have.
上次给你的呢?
What happened to the last ones I gave you?
什么?
Sorry?
我最后给你的一瓶  应该还剩20颗的
The last bottle I gave you. there should be 20 left.
你在筹划一次旅行?
Are you planning a trip?
拜托了  你就给我就是了
Please, just give me the vitamins.
你要去哪  Sun?
Where are you going,Sun?
我们要去Locke的营地
We're going to Locke's camp.
什么?
What?
因为我不相信这些人
Because I don't trust these people.
不管信还是不信  你哪都不能去
Whether you trust them or not, you can't go there.
Locke不准备离开这个岛
Locke doesn't want to leave the island,
我和你讲过的  Sun  孕妇...
And I've told you, sun, pregnant women...
她们在这都没法活下去
They don't survive here.
是的  你的确对我说过
Yes, you did tell me that.
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
听着  我知道我来这后
Look, I know that I have been less than truthful
很多事情都撒了谎
About certain things since coming here,
但我保证  Sun  我向你保证...
But I promise you, sun, I promise you...
在这件事上我没撒谎
I'm not lying about this.
在你向我吐露心声后
After everything you've confided in me,
你至少得信任我
I should at least have your trust.
Claire的孩子好好的
Claire's baby is fine.
我也感觉很正常
I feel fine.
只是你的那些我会出事的故事让我不安
All I have are your stories that I'm going to get sick.
怎么做对我和我的孩子最好  我就会怎么做
I'm going to do what's best for me and for my baby,
因为  不...
Because, no...
我不信任你
I don't trust you.
没事的  不会有事的
It's okey. It's going to be okay.
她是...?
Is that...?
是的  大洋航班六个幸存者之一.
Yes. Oceanic Six.
停下  你要干嘛?
Stop! What are you doing?
我们都会把珠宝拿下的
We remove all jewelry.
怕感染啊
It's for the swelling.
不  不要把我的戒指拿下来!
No! Not my ring!
我们会替你保管好的
Nothing will happen to it.
没事的
It's okay.
Kwon女士  我是Bae医生
Mrs. Kwon, I'm Dr. Bae.
我为Park医生代班
I'm on duty for Dr. Park.
他在哪?  发生什么事了?
Where is he? What's happening?
他开会去了
He's away at a conference...
给她来点止痛的
Give her something for the pain.
来  让我检查一下...
Now let me take a look...
孩子有什么问题吗?
Is something wrong with my baby?
孩子现在很危险
It is in distress.
怎么回事?
What's wrong?
我还不确定
I don't know yet.
我马上查查
That's what I'm going to find out.
还要联系什么人吗?
Is there anyone we should contact?
你丈夫?  你父母?
You husband? Your parents?
联系Jin...  我丈夫...
Just get Jin...  my husband...
Jin...
叫Jin来吧...
Just get Jin...
我会尽力联系上他的
I'll try to reach him.
联系我...丈夫...
Get my...husband...
我肯定他很快就会到
I'm sure he'll be here soon.
Jin...
出租车
Taxi
我是  我在路上了...  喂?
Yes, I'm on my way...Hello?
喂...
Hello...
嘿  搞什么啊?
Hey! What is this?
停车
Stop!
混蛋!
You bastard!
要是让我碰见
I will kill you.
我要杀了你!
If I find you!
我要找到你  把你的头扭下来
I will hunt you down and rip your head off!
我要再买个熊猫!
I need another panda!
很抱歉  都卖完了
I'm sorry, that was the last one.
那个呢?
What about that one?
就你后面
It's right behind you!
那个已经被人订了
That one is on hold.
这些熊猫很受欢迎
They're quite popular.
你要多少?
How much do you want?
人家钱都付过了
It's already paid for.
这个...
What about this..
今年是龙年,
In the year of the dragon,
它会带来好运的
It brings good luck.
我需要那只熊猫
I need the panda.
不要再丢了
Don't lose this one.
只要走到小溪那
Once you hit the stream,
你们就往西北走
You wanna head northwest,
-基本都是直线  大概一天半就可以到  -谢谢
Pretty much in a straight line for about a day and a half. thank you.
我得跟Jack说一声
I'm gonna have to tell jack.
不过我会让你们先走远的
But I'll give you guys a nice, long head start.
我本应跟他说  但他不会理解的
I'd tell him myself, but he wouldn't understand.
是的  他不会的
No, he wouldn't
你得走了
You'd better get going
-路上小心  -谢谢
-Be safe, okay? -Thank you.
她哪里都别想去
She's not going anywhere.
Sun  这不是个好主意
Sun,this is a bad idea.
关你什么事?
What concern is it of yours?
你知道你妻子现在的身体状况吗?
Do you understand your wife's medical condition right now?
帮我翻译
Translate for me.
不
No.
你的妻子身体很弱
Your wife is very sick.
要是她不能在三周内离开这个岛
If she doesn't get off this island in three weeks,
她就会死
She will die.
要是你让她走
If you let her go,
你的妻子就会有危险
Your wife is in danger.
Jin...  危险
Jin... danger.
不论她去哪里..
Wherever sun go..
我都会陪着她的
I go.
求你了.
Please.
Jin
Jin.
你的妻子有外遇
Your wife had an affair.
什么?
What?
Sun和别的男人上过床
Sun was with another man.
她觉得孩子是那个人的
She thought the baby was his.
Jin...
别不理我  听我解释
Talk to me. Let me explain.
已经很久了
It was a lone time ago.
看着我
Look at me.
看着我啊
Just look at me.
我知道你很生气
I understand you're angry.
我不会去找什么借口的
And I have no excuse.
请听我解释啊
Please let me explain.
你听我解释啊
let me explain.
Jin...
嘿  你去钓鱼吗
Hey. you are fishing?
嗯  你介意我一起去吗
Uh, do you mind if i... tag along?
对不起  我不是故意打扰你们的
Oh, I am sorry. i-i didn't mean to interrupt.
没有  一起去吧
No. come.
你说真的?
You sure?
一起吧
Come.
你发现了吗？我们是这个岛上唯一的两对夫妇
You realize we're the only two married guys on the island?
结过婚的
Married.
不  不是说我们  不是
Yeah, well, no, not to each other. no.
你应该明白的
You got it.
很不容易  对吧
It's not easy, iit?
我的意思是   很奇妙
Oh, I mean, it's--it's wonderful,
但是  让我们面对现实
But... let's face it.
做每个决定你都得花两倍的时间
Every decision that you make takes twice as long
因为你总得说服她们
Cause you always gotta talk them into it.
得了癌症
Has cancer.
她病得厉害
She's sick.
快死了
Dying.
至少她之前快不行了
Well, at least, she was dying.
她说她现在好点了
She says she's better now.
她说是因为这个地方...
She says it's this place...
这个岛  让她好起来
The island.
但当我们内部开始分裂得时候
But when the camp split up,
我知道她肯定会跟着Locke走
I was sure that she'd want to go with locke.
她怎么会愿意冒再次生病得危险
Why would she want to leave the island
离开这座岛呢？
And risk getting sick again?
那你为什么还要Jack这边?
Uh, then why do you stay with jack?
因为这样做是对的
Because it was the right thing to do.
Locke?
他是个杀人犯
He's a murderer.
看到了吧  这些全是因果报应  Jin
See, it's all about karma, jin.
你知道什么是因果报应吗
Do you know karma?
你做了不好的选择  不好的事情就会发生
You make bad choices, bad things happen to you.
但如果你做了正确的选择  好的事情就会发生
But you make good choices, and then good--
你钓到了一条
Hey! hey, hey, hey! you got one.
就在那儿  使劲拉
Yeah. here, pull it .
哇  看看
Wow, look at that!
看到了吗?  这就是因果报应
Ah, you see? now that's karma.
我们肯定都是好人  对吧
We must be the good guys, huh?
还要等多久啊？
How long's that gonna go on for, eh?
他妈的  他们就找出是什么故障原因吗？
Can't they just fix whatever the bloody hell's causing that?
那不是机器发出的声音
That sound is not mechanical.
什么  你认为是有人故意弄出的声音
What, you think somebody's doing that?
有人在那管子上敲来敲去？
Somebody's just banging those pipes again and again?
就是这样
That's exactly what I think.
先生们
Gentlemen...
谢谢你们的耐心
Thanks for your patience.
船长现在能见你们了
The captain would like to see you now.
直升机哪去了?
Where's the helicopter?
Lapidus开去执行任务去了
Lapidus is running an errand.
什么任务
What kind of errand?
我只是个医生  我不知道他去哪儿了
I'm a doctor. I don't know where he's going.
他回岛上了?
Did he go to the island?
你认为他还有什么地方可以去吗
You know anywhere else he could land?
他去做什么
What's he going to do?
我说了  我只是个医生
I said I'm just a doctor.
Lapidus有留下什么话吗?
What did lapidus say?
-他什么都没说  -她在干什么
He didn't say anything. what is she doing?!
那个女人刚刚从船上跳下去了
That woman just jumped over the side of the ship!
别傻站在那  你们他妈的怎么了？
Don't just stand there! what's the matter with you people?!
拿绳子来  你们怎么都不动啊  拿绳子来
Get a rope! why aren'tou doing anything?! bring a rope!
绳子!  拿绳子!
Get a rope! get a pe!
-好了  -她刚刚跳下去了
Stop! she just jumped!
结束了  她已经死了
It's over. she's gone.
每个人都回到自己的岗位去
Everybody get back to your posts.
这是命令
That was an order.
我是Gault船长
I'm captain gault.
我猜你们两个有点想不通吧
I suppose you two have a few questions.
-我有什么能帮你们  -什么?
So what can I do for you? what?
-你们说想跟我谈谈  -就从刚才那事说起
You boys said you wanted to speak with me. let's just start with
为什么一个女人跳海了却没有人去阻止她
Why a woman jumped over side of your ship,and you did nothing to stop it
我没有跳也没有命令我的船员跳
I didn't jump or order my crew to jump in
因为我不想再失去更多人
Because I didn't want to lose any more peoe.
这里到底发生了什么
What exactly is going on here?
我的一些船员感染了一种
Some of my crew has been dealing with...
怎么说呢
What might best be described
一种叫幽居病的病
As a heightened case of cabin fever.
我认为这跟靠近这个岛屿的原因有关
I think it's got something to do
那为什么你不掉头？
With the close proximity of the island. why don't you turn around, then?
我试过了  但是有个船上有个破坏者
I've tried, but we have a saboteur on board,
他在引擎上做了手脚
And he's de one hell a job on my engines.
我已经叫我的船员加班加点地去维修了
I've got my creworking around the clock to repair them.
然后你就会带我们的人回去？
And then you'll take our people home?
然后我们转移到安全的水域
Then we move to safer waters.
这是我所有的命令
That all are my orders.
你大概不会告诉我们  谁下了这些命令？
And I don't suppose you'll tell us who gave you those orders?
当然会  是Charles Widmore
Sure, I ll. charles widmore.
这是Charles Widmore的船？
This is charles widmore's boat?
对  你认识他的
That's right. you know him.
你们有人知道这是什么吗?
Do either of you know what this is?
是一个飞行数据记录器  就是俗话说的黑匣子
It's a flight data recorder, otherwise known as a black box.
对  就是黑匣子
That's exactly what it is.
有意思的是
Now here's the funny thing.
这是大洋航空815航班上的黑匣子
This black box comes from oceanic flight 8-1-5.
一艘打捞船从海底打捞出来的
A salvage vessel recovered it from the bottom of the ocean.
Widmore先生耗费了大量的人力财力
It took a considerable amount of mr. widmore's resources
才搞到手
To procure it.
这个黑匣子是在一起空难中发现
It was found with the wreckage of the plane,
324名乘客全部死亡
Along with all 324 dead passengers.
然而故事还没完
That's not the complete story,
你们都清楚 Jarrah先生
As you are well aware, mr. jarrah,
你们活生生地站在这里
Given the fact that you're standing here, breathing.
那次空难很明显是计划好的
The wreckage was obviously staged.
现在你们可以想象一下
Now can you imagine what kind of resources and manpower
花了多少人力物力才制造了这个假象
Go into pulling off a feat of that magnitude?
空难的假象
Faking the recovery of a plane crash?
让324个家庭因为一个谎言
Putting 324 families through a grieving process
痛不欲生?
Based on a lie?
但是更烦人的事
But what's even more disturbing--
到底在哪里才能让一个人
Where exactly does one come across
发现324个人的尸体
324 dead bodies?
Jarrah先生  Hume先生
And that, mr. jarrah, mr. hume,
那  就是我们要找到Benjamin Linus
Is just one of the many reasons
的原因之一
We want benjamin linus.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不得不想尽办法来阻止你
I had to stop you any way I could.
这不是你的地盘  你没权阻止我
It wasn't your place to stop us
我知道你不相信我
I know you don't trust me,
但是你需要离开这座岛  我们都需要
But you need tget off is island. we all do.
你想离开？
You want to leave?
做梦都想
More than anything.
我不知道那边那艘船能不能带我们离开
I don't know if that boat out there is the answer or not,
但总有一丝希望
But it's something.
我需要回家
I need to go home.
你也是
So do you.
Sun
Sun...
再接下来的三周里
In about three weeks,
你会不断的出现想呕吐的现象
You'll be in an almost constant state of nausea.
在那之后的一周里  你会感觉到呼吸急促
A week after that, you will experience shortness of breath
并且会持续很久
That won't go away.
在那之后的又一周  你会失去意识
A week after that, you will lose consciousness
并且昏迷
And slip into a coma.
再之后  Sun  你会死的
And then, sun, you will die.
当你的心脏停止跳动时
And when your heart stops beating...
肚子里的孩子也活不了了
So will the baby's.
Sun  这就是我为什么要阻止你
And that, sun, is why it is my business,
因为你是我的病人
Because you are my patient.
如果你真的去了
If you go...
你会死的
You will die...
然后你的孩子就没了
And your baby will never be born.
我得做个破腹产
I have to perform a C-section
不要
No
你不知道
You don't understand...
使用药物就很难顺产的
The medication makes a natural birth difficult
不  不行  要等到JIN...
No, no! Not until Jin
我们必须做手术了
We've got to get to surgery!
我的丈夫在哪里
Where's my husband?
他还没到
He's not here yet.
我们不能等了
We cannot wait
Jin
Bae医生
Dr.Bae
婴儿的头出来了
The baby is crowning
好的 sun  你现在要开始使劲了
Okay, Sun. You need to push now.
对  就这样  使劲  使劲
That's it...Push! Push!
你能做到的
You can do it!
就这样  使劲
That's it...Push!
你做到了
You did it
恭喜
Congratulation
是个女孩
You have a baby daughter.
你觉得船长怎样?
So what'd you think of the captain?
出奇的友好
He was surprisingly forthcoming.
还真是那么回事  别让他溜了
Yeah, he tell it like it is. just don't piss him off.
你知道我的意思吗?
You know what I mean?
我想你会喜欢你的房间的
I think you'll like your room.
在船上算是安静的地方了
It's on a quiet part of the ship.
这船没动
Th ship isn't moving.
好吧  如果你非要这么说
Well, if you say so.
那玩意儿怎么还在那  该死
That shouldn't still be there. damn it.
Johns  是你吗
Hey, johns. it that you?
Johnson?
来把这儿整理干净
Mop this up.
抱歉  我得马上到甲板去
Sorry. I gotta go up on deck.
不行!  到这儿来把它整理干净
No, you're gonna mop this up!
Kevin  这是...
Kevin, this is, uh...
我是Sayid
S-sayid.
我叫Kevin Johnson
Kevin johnson.
很高兴见到你  Kevin
Nice to meet you, kevin.
我晚饭做了
I made... dinner.
我以为你不理我了
I thought you had left me.
你会听我解释吗?
Will you let me try to explain?
这无关紧要了
It won't matter.
听着  可能...
Just listen, maybe...
我知道你为什么这样做
I know why you did it.
我了解
I know the man...
来到这岛上之前的
I used to be.
所作所为
Before this island.
我克制自己的感情...
I withheld my affections...
我还知道...
And I know...
你所做的一切
that whatever you did...
你和那个男人所做的事
you did to that man.
都是他造成的
His action caused this.
所以我原谅你
so I forgive you.
我要同你一起去Locke的营地
So I will go to Locke's camp with you.
我不去了
I don't want to go there anymore.
Juliet说得很有道理
Juliet was very convincing.
我们必须离开这个岛
We have to get off this island.
那些人有直升机
These people had a helicopter.
我们必须试一试
We have to try.
我会竭尽全力地保护你和孩子的
I'll do all it to protect you and the baby.
我保证
I promise.
还有件事
There's just one thing.
请你跟我说实话
And please, the truth...
说吧
Anything.
这孩子
Is... the baby...
是我的吗?
Mine?
是的  Jin
Yes,Jin.
我发誓这孩子是你的
I swear the baby is yours.
是你的孩子
It's yours.
我真的很爱你
I love you very much.
我以为我失去你了
I thought I had lost you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
我会永远守护你
And you will never lose me.
我是Jin-Soo Kwon
I am Jin-Soo Kwon.
我是代表Paik汽车公司来的
I represent Paik Automotive.
有什么事
Yes.
我听说大使当爷爷了
I heard the Ambassador is now a grandfather.
我是来送礼物的
I came to present a gift.
在这等一下
Wait here.
请问一下
Excuse me.
是男孩还是女孩
Is it a boy or a girl?
男孩
A boy.
大使先生
Mr Ambassodor...
我们用这熊猫以表Paik先生
This panda is a symbol of Mr. Paik's eagerness...
想同贵国做生意的迫切愿望
to do business in the great country of China.
请您接受他的祝贺
Please accept his congratulations.
替我谢谢Paik先生
Thank Mr. Paik for me.
告诉他我会致电感谢
Tell him I'll call.
这么快就要走了?
Leaving so soon?
那不是我的孩子
It wasn't my baby.
是这样啊  也许哪天...
Well, maybe someday...
我没这么快
Don't rush me.
我才结婚两个月
I've been married two months.
真没想到你大老远跑过来
I can't believe you came all this way.
是吗?  还有谁要来吗
Are you kidding? is anyone else coming?
很好
Good.
那么... 她在哪
So... where is she?
这边
Come here.
她很可爱
She's awesome.
谢谢
Thank you.
要不要抱抱吗
Would you like to hold her?
我不想  我没有那样柔软的手
I don'know. i... I kind of have two lt hands.
我相信你
I trust you.
她看起来很像Jin
She looks just like jin.
是啊...
Yes...
的确像
She does.
我想我们该去看看他
I guess we should, like, go see him.
当然
Of course.
Jin...
你说对了
You were right.
是个女孩
It's a girl.
分娩时我很痛苦...
The delivery was hard on me...
医生说我那时我还大叫你的名字...
The doctor said I was calling out for you...
我真希望你能在那
I wish you could've been there.
Jin...
她很可爱
She's beautiful.
叫Ji Yeon
Ji Yeon
我给她取了你想好的名字
I named her just like you wanted.
我很想你
I miss you so much.